{
	"quiz": {
		"movies": {
			"q1": {
				"question": "Which of these great movies was made first?",
				"options": [
					"Star Wars",
					"Citizen Kane",
					"Casablanca",
					"Lawrence of Arabia"
				],
				"answer": "Citizen Kane"
			},
			"q2": {
				"question": "Judy Garland played Dorothy Gale in what movie?",
				"options": [
					"Gone with the Wind",
					"A Streetcar Named Desire",
					"The Wizard of Oz",
					"Peter Pan"
				],
				"answer": "The Wizard of Oz"
			},
			"q3": {
				"question": "What was the name of the mechanical shark used to film JAWS?",
				"options": [
					"Bruce",
					"Fred",
					"Chomps",
					"Larry"
				],
				"answer": "Bruce"
			},
			"q4": {
				"question": "Which movie earned Tom Hanks an Oscar in 1994?",
				"options": [
					"Saving Private Ryan",
					"You've Got Mail",
					"Castaway",
					"Forrest Gump"
				],
				"answer": "Forrest Gump"
			}
		},
		"music": {
			"q1": {
				"question": "Who makes the Stratocaster guitar?",
				"options": [
					"Gibson",
					"Fender",
					"Smiths",
					"Martin"
				],
				"answer": "Fender"
			},
			"q2": {
				"question": "Who composed the classical piece \"Peter and the Wolf \"?",
				"options": [
					"Prokofiev",
					"Tchaikovsy",
					"Rachmaninoff",
					"Stravinsky"
				],
				"answer": "Prokofiev"
			},
			"q3": {
				"question": "How many strings does a standard violin have?",
				"options": [
					"Three",
					"Four",
					"Five",
					"Six"
				],
				"answer": "Four"
			},
			"q4": {
				"question": "What record label did The Beatles establish?",
				"options": [
					"Liverpool",
					"Apple",
					"MopTop",
					"Strawberry Fields"
				],
				"answer": "Apple"
			}
		},
		"sports": {
			"q1": {
				"question": "How many players are on the field during a game of American football?",
				"options": [
					"14",
					"18",
					"20",
					"22"
				],
				"answer": "22"
			},
			"q2": {
				"question": "Who owns the blimps that fly over sporting events?",
				"options": [
					"Michelin",
					"U.S. Air Force",
					"Goodyear",
					"Budweiser"
				],
				"answer": "Goodyear"
			},
			"q3": {
				"question": "What male tennis player has won the most Grand Slam titles?",
				"options": [
					"Federer",
					"Agassi",
					"Connors",
					"McEnroe"
				],
				"answer": "Federer"
			},
			"q4": {
				"question": "Which movie earned Tom Hanks an Oscar in 1994?",
				"options": [
					"Saving Private Ryan",
					"You've Got Mail",
					"Castaway",
					"Forrest Gump"
				],
				"answer": "Forrest Gump"
			}
		},
		"books": {
			"q1": {
				"question": "Who wrote the book about the wolf/dog \"White Fang\"?",
				"options": [
					"Jack London",
					"Mark Twain",
					"Edgar Allen Poe",
					"Jules Verne"
				],
				"answer": "Jack London"
			},
			"q2": {
				"question": "\"The Hound of the Baskervilles\" stars which fictional detective?",
				"options": [
					"Poirot",
					"Wolfe",
					"Marple",
					"Holmes"
				],
				"answer": "Holmes"
			},
			"q3": {
				"question": "Samuel Langhorne Clemens is better known by what pen name?",
				"options": [
					"Mark Twain",
					"James Patterson",
					"Stephen King",
					"James Fenimore Cooper"
				],
				"answer": "Mark Twain"
			},
			"q4": {
				"question": "Who wrote \"The Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe\"?",
				"options": [
					"Ernest Hemingway",
					"C.S. Lewis",
					"Charles Dickens",
					"H.G. Wells"
				],
				"answer": "C.S. Lewis"
			}
		}
	}
}